Zeitgeist: The Movie is a documentary, history film directed by Peter Joseph.
A documentary examining possible historical and modern conspiracies surrounding
Christianity, the 9/11 terrorist attacks, and the Federal Reserve bank.
Self (voice) (archive sound), played by Chögyam Trungpa.
Self (voice) (archive sound), played by Jordan Maxwell.
Self (voice) (archive sound), played by George Carlin.
Self (voice) (archive sound), played by Bill Hicks.
Self (archive footage), played by David Ray Griffin.
Self (archive footage), played by Joseph Casaliggi.
Zeitgeist is a series of three documentary films released between 2007 and 2011 that present a number
of conspiracy theories, as well as proposals for broad social and economic changes.
The films, Zeitgeist: The Movie (2007), Zeitgeist: Addendum (2008) and
Zeitgeist: Moving Forward (2011) are all directed by Peter Joseph.
The film explores themes of corruption, nazi, war on
terror, world war ii, economic theory.